cyberwurx.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy | Cyber Wurx Datacenter

Cyber Wurx LLC and any subsidiaries of Cyber Wurx LLC recognize the importance of our customers trust. Keeping our customers’ personal information confidential is a top priority for Cyber Wurx LLC. Cyber Wurx will limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum requirements needed to administer our products and services. Additionally Cyber Wurx adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union (EU) which can be found here: <http://export.gov/safeharbor/>

**Types of data collected when visiting our website(s)**  
When you visit our website, our server logs collect the following information. This information is collected for development and marketing purposes.

  1. Internet protocol address (also known as IP address or network address)
  2. Cookies (A cookie is a unique alphanumeric identifier that determines the number of users that visit our website) If you do not wish for cookies to be placed on your computer, they can be disabled in the security section of your web browser. Disabling cookies will disable some functionality of the Cyber Wurx website.
  3. State/country from which you accessed our site
  4. Type of web browser
  5. Date and time of your visit
  6. Internet service provider
  7. Link of website that you accessed our site
  8. Links visited within our site

**Types of data collected in online and offline communications**  
When inquiring about our services via telephone, email, web forms or other methods of communication, we may ask for the following information: Your name, company name, telephone number, and email address. The information collected is used to provide service and support.

**Types of data collected if you open an account**  
Contact and Payment information:

  1. Name
  2. Company Name if applicable
  3. Street Address
  4. City
  5. State, Province or Region
  6. Country
  7. Zip or Postal code
  8. Telephone Number(s)
  9. E-mail address
  10. Order information
  11. Credit card or ACH information

Contact and payment information are collected upon opening an account and be used in the following manner.

  * Service and technical support purposes
  * Network maintenance notifications
  * Server maintenance notifications
  * Billing purposes
  * AUP violations
  * Promotional specials

Payment information, such as credit card or ACH, is stored securely and only used for payment of products, services and overages. This information is only shared with credit card clearing houses and banking institutions as a means to process your payment.

**How we share your personal data**  
Your personal data is only accessible by Cyber Wurx employees or contractors who are bound by a confidentiality agreement. Your information is not shared in any other way unless ordered by a court of law or in connection with a sale or transfer of ownership.

**Customer Center and Opt-out**  
Upon account activation you will be given secure access to our customer portal located at[https://customer.cyberwurx.com](https://customer.cyberwurx.com/)

The customer center allows the account owner to make changes to:

  * Contact information
  * Payment information
  * Add or delete an authorized contact
  * Ability to opt-out of newsletters or promos

Please note that some e-mail notifications do not include the opt-out option. These include, but are not limited to the following:

  * Billing notices
  * Network maintenance and upgrades
  * Server maintenance
  * Legal notices

**Security of Data**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 314-849-4698 or via  [contact form](http://www.cyberwurx.com/contact.html).**

**Links to other websites**  
We may provide links to websites that are not affiliated with Cyber Wurx. The privacy practices of these websites may differ from the Cyber Wurx privacy practices. Since we are not responsible for a non-affiliated website.s privacy practices, you are encouraged to review their privacy policy before submitting personal information.

**Policy Updates**  
The Privacy Statement may be updated from time to time. Changes to the Privacy Statement will be posted on the Cyber Wurx website. Changes to the Privacy Statement will never be less protective without prior written e-mail notification.

**Enforcement of Privacy Statement**  
Cyber Wurx verifies that the Privacy Statement is up to date, prominently displayed and conforms to the Safe Harbor Principles. We encourage customers to raise any concerns you may have with the protection or misuse of your personal data via [contact form](http://www.cyberwurx.com/contact.html).
